D.A军字幕组 诚译
D.A军字幕组长期招募:字译 听译 时间轴/后期 压制/发布,有意者请加微信18198102499或QQ群:665892095(哈迷优先)
翻译： 月咏零 Jack 小新 我庄严宣誓 夜雪 Maggie 陌凉 枝梧 谦之  \n丫蛋 灌汤包 佳妮 猫格子 丛格格 珂儿 魏申鲸 圆脸的瘦子 万凌宇
校对： 潇湘竹叶 火箭浣熊 Twig斯内普 Eunice_ET 橙子 Leslie
时间轴： Twig斯内普 陌凉 Gaopighaha 神秘人
压制： 格林德沃
美国魔法部
纽约 1927
You'll be glad to be rid of him, I expect.
你很开心能够摆脱他吧  我想
We'd be more than happy to keep him here in custody.
我们更希望他能够继续在牢里关着
Six months are enough.
六个月已经足够了
It's time for him to answer for his crimes in Europe.
他是时候为他在欧洲犯下的罪行担上责任了
President Picquery, Mr. Spielman, sir.
皮克科瑞主席 斯皮尔曼先生
Prisoner is secured and ready to travel.
犯人已经准备好转移了
You've thrown everything at him, I see.
你们把能用的招都用上了
It was necessary. He's extremely powerful.
这很有必要 他太强大了
We've had to change his guard three times, he's very... persuasive.
我们换了三次守卫 他嘴皮子非常厉害
So we removed his tongue.
所以我们割掉了他的舌头
Grindelwald! Grindelwald!
格林德沃 格林德沃
The wizarding community worldwide owes you a great debt, Madam President.
全球的巫师界都欠你一个人情 主席女士
Do not underestimate him.
不要小看他
Mr. Spielman, we found his wand hidden away.
斯皮尔曼先生 我们刚发现他藏起来的魔杖
Abernathy?
阿伯内西
And we found this.
我们还找到这个
No more silver tongue, hmm?
还油嘴滑舌吗 嗯?
You have joined a noble cause, my friend.
我的朋友 你加入了一项高尚的事业
I know. I know. I know, Antonio
安东尼奥 我知道 我知道
So needy.
太饥渴了
神奇动物：格林德沃之罪 加长版
英国伦敦
英国魔法部
三个月后
They're ready for you, Newt.
他们准备好了 纽特
Leta…
莉塔
What are you doing here?
你在这里做什么
Theseus thought it would be good if I became part of the Ministry family.
忒修斯认为我成为魔法部大家族的一员是个很好的主意
Did he actually say the words “Ministry family”?
他真的用了“大家族”这个词吗
That sounds like my brother
不愧是他
Theseus was disappointed you couldn't come to dinner.
你没来吃晚餐 忒修斯很失望
Any of the nights we've asked you.
每次问你你都没空
Well, I've been busy.
我一直很忙
He's your brother, Newt.
他是你的哥哥 纽特
He likes spending time with you.
他喜欢跟你在一起
And so do I.
我也是
Oi, you! Hop in, Pick.
嘿 皮克 跳进来
Why do strange creatures love you so much?
为什么那些奇奇怪怪的生物那么喜欢你
Well, there are no strange creatures... - Only blinkered people!
唔  没有什么奇奇怪怪的生物... -只有心胸狭隘的人
How long did you get in detention for saying that to Prendergast?
你说完这个之后被普伦德加斯特留堂了多久
You know, I think it was a month that time.
好像是一个月吧 那一次
And I set off a Dung bomb under his desk so I could join you, do you remember?
记得吗 我为了跟你一起还在他桌子底下设了个粪蛋
No, I actually don't remember that.
不是很记得了
Hello.
你们好啊
Theseus. We were just talking about Newt coming for dinner
忒修斯 我们刚才在说纽特会来一起享用晚餐
Really? Well…
喔 真的吗
Look, before we go in there I
听着 在我们进去之前 我...
It's my fifth attempt, Theseus. I know the form.
忒修斯 这都第五次了 我知道程序
This isn't going to be like the other times. This is…
这次跟其他的不一样 这次...
Just try and keep an open mind, will you?
心态尽量放开点 好吗
And maybe a little less. - Like me?
然后尽量不要那么… -像我自己
Well, it can't hurt.
又不会少一块肉
Come on. Let's go.
嘿 进来吧
Hearing commences…
听证会开始
You want an end to the ban on your traveling internationally. Why?
你希望我们终止对你国际旅行的禁令 为什么呢
Because I like to travel internationally.
因为我喜欢国际旅行
Subject uncooperative and evasive on reasons for last international trip.
申请人拒绝合作并刻意回避回答上次国际旅行的原因
It was a field trip.
那次只是一次实地考察
So I was collecting material for my book on magical beasts
我在为我关于神奇动物的书收集资料
You destroyed half of New York.
你毁了半个纽约
-No, that's actually factually incorrect on two counts
-不对 实际上有两个方面不正确 -纽特
Mr. Scamander, it's clear you're frustrated and
斯卡曼德先生 显然你很困扰
frankly, so are we
坦白说, 我们也是
In the spirit of compromise, we'd like to make a proposition.
折中一点 我们想达成一个协议
What kind of proposition?
什么样的协议
The committee will agree to lift your travel ban under one condition.
答应一个条件 委员会就终止你的旅行禁令
You join the Ministry.
你加入魔法部
Specifically, your brother's department.
准确来说 加入你哥哥的部门
No.
不行
I…I think that… Theseus is the Auror
我觉得忒修斯比较适合做傲罗
I think my talents lie elsewhere.
我认为我另有所长
Mr. Scamander, The wizarding and non-wizarding
斯卡曼德先生 巫师和非巫师世界的和平
worlds have been at peace for over a century.
已经持续了一个多世纪了
Grindelwald wants to see that peace destroyed.
格林德沃想摧毁这份和平
And for certain members of our community
对于我们社会的某些人来说
his message is very seductive
他的思想是十分吸引人的
Many pure-bloods believe it is their birthright to rule
很多纯血认为他们生为统治者
not only our world but the non-magic world as well.
不只是在巫师界 在麻瓜世界亦是
They see Grindelwald as their hero,
他们认格林德沃为领导者
and Grindelwald sees this boy
而格林德沃将这个男孩
as a means to make this all come true.
看作能使这一切成为现实的手段
I'm sorry. You're talking about Credence as if he were still here.
抱歉 你说的好像克雷登斯还在世一样
He survived, Newt.
纽特 他活了下来
He is still alive.
他还活着
He left New York months ago.
几个月前他离开了纽约
He's somewhere in Europe. Where exactly, we don't know, but…
他在欧洲的某个地方 我们不知道确切地点 但是...
And you want me to hunt Credence down?
你们希望我去抓他
To kill him?
去杀了他?
Same old Scamander.
还是老样子啊 斯卡曼德
What's he doing here?
他在这里干什么
Taking on the job you're too soft to do.
接手软弱的你不敢做的任务
Is that it?
就这样吗?
Travel documentation denied.
拒绝通过旅行档案
Newt!
纽特
You think I like the idea of Grimmson any more than you do?
你以为我会喜欢格里姆森的主意吗
Listen, I don't want to hear how the ends justify the means, Theseus.
听着 忒修斯 我不想听什么结果胜于手段如何如何
I think you're gonna have to pull your head out of the sand!
你不能再像鸵鸟把自己的头埋在沙子里似的逃避现实
Okay, right, here we go. What a selfish... irresponsible…
啊, 对, 又来了. 多么自私...不负责任...
You know, the time is coming when everyone’s
那个时代快来临了 每一个人
everyone's gonna have to pick a side.
每一个人 都要选边站
Even you.
连你也一样
I don't do sides.
我不站边的
Newt. Newt.
纽特 纽特
C’mere.
过来
They are watching you.
他们时时刻刻都在盯着你
Well, gentlemen.
好吧 先生们
I assume this means I have the job.
我想 这代表这份任务 归我了
法国 巴黎
(法语) 宝贝
(法语) 外面是谁?
This will be suitable after a thorough cleanse.
彻底清理之后 这里就会变得很舒适了
I want you to go to the circus now.
我希望你现在就动身去马戏团
Give my note to Credence,
把我的信带给克雷登斯
begin his journey.
开始他的旅程
When we've won, they'll flee cities in the millions.
等我们赢了 有成千上万的人会逃走
They've had their time.
他们得意得够久了
We don't say such things out loud.
这些事情不需要我们大声说出来
We want only freedom.
我们只想要自由
Freedom to be ourselves.
可以做自己的自由
To annihilate non-wizards.
还要消灭不会魔法的人
Not all of them. Not all.
不是他们所有人 不全是
We're not merciless.
我们还不至于那么无情
The beast of burden will always be necessary.
任何时候都需要用来干活的牲畜
梅里恩街
Ventus.
风旋骤卷
Dumbledore.
邓布利多
Were the less conspicuous rooftops full, then?
你非得站在这么显眼的屋顶上吗?
I do enjoy a view.
我确实很喜欢欣赏风景
Nebulus.
云雾缥缈
How was it?
怎么样了
They're still convinced that you sent me to New York.
他们仍然坚信是你派我去纽约的
You told them I didn't?
你说不是我?
Yes.
是的
Evening.
晚安
Even though you did.
虽然确实是你
You told me where to find that trafficked Thunderbird,
是你告诉我哪里可以找到那只被交易的雷鸟
Dumbledore. You knew that I would take him home
邓布利多 你清楚我会带他回家
and you knew I'd have to take him through a Muggle port.
你也知道我只能用麻瓜的交通工具带他走
Well, I've always felt an affinity with the great magical birds..
嗯 我总觉得我和那些有强大魔力的鸟类有亲切感
There's a story in my family
在我家族中有一个传说
that a phoenix will come to any Dumbledore who is in desperate need.
邓布利多家族的人有急切需要时 凤凰就会出现
They say my great-great grandfather had one, but that it took flight when he died,
据说我的曾祖父就有一只 但是自从他去世后
never to return.
凤凰就再也没有出现过
With all due respect, I don't believe for a minute
恕我冒昧 教授 我绝对不相信
that's why you told me about the Thunderbird.
这就是你告诉我雷鸟的原因
删剪片段
Why did you send me to New York?
你为什么要送我去纽约
Because I knew Grindelwald would try to catch Credence.
因为我知道格林德沃会试图抓住克雷登斯
He had a vision, you see, many years ago
你要知道 多年以前 他就预知
In which an Obscurial killed a man he fears above all others
一个默然者杀死了他最害怕的人
You.
就是你
I thought you might deprive Grindelwald of his weapon.
我觉得你能消灭格林德沃的武器
Not by killing Credence, but by saving him.
不过不是要杀死克雷登斯 而是拯救他
Credence is in Paris, Newt.
克雷登斯在巴黎 纽特
He's trying to trace his real family.
他在寻找到自己真正的家族
I take it.
这我信
You've heard the rumors about who he really is?
我估计你已听说 关于他真实身分的传闻
No.
并没有
The pure-bloods think he's the last of an important French line,
纯血家族认为他是法国一个重要家族最后的血脉
a baby whom everyone thought lost
他们认为 他在婴儿时期就失踪了
- Not Leta's brother? - That's what they're whispering.
-那不是指莉塔的弟弟吧? -大家是这么想的
Pure-blood or not, I know this...
无论是不是纯血 我知道
An Obscurus grows in the absence of love
默默然是因为缺少关爱而产生的
as a dark twin, an only friend.
只能终日与黑暗为伴
If Credence has a real brother or sister out there that can take its place,
如果克雷登斯真的有亲生的兄弟姐妹能够代替默默然
he might yet be saved.
他也许还有救
Wherever Credence is in Paris, he's either in danger
不论他在巴黎的何处 若不是身处险境
or a danger to others.
就是会危害他人
We may not know who he is yet, but he needs to be found.
我们仍然不知道他到底是谁 但是我们必须找到他
And I rather hoped you might be the one to find him.
我希望你能找到他
What's that?
这是什么
An address of a very old acquaintance of mine.
这是我一个老熟人的地址
A safe house in Paris, reinforced with enchantments.
这是巴黎的一处安全屋 用魔法进行保护
Safe house? Why would I need a safe house in Paris?
安全屋 我为什么需要在巴黎用安全屋
One hopes you won't, but should things at some point go terribly wrong
我也希望你用不上 但是凡事总会有意外
it's good to have a place to go.
有地方去总是件好事
You know, for a cup of tea.
至少能喝杯茶 你懂的
No, no, no, absolutely not.
不 不 不 绝对不行
I'm banned from international travel, Dumbledore.
我被禁止出境旅行 邓布利多
If I leave the country, they will put me in Azkaban and throw away the key.
如果我离开英国 他们就会把我丢进阿兹卡班 然后把钥匙丢了
Do you know why I admire you, Newt? -Why?
你知道为什么我如此喜欢你吗 纽特? -为什么?
More, perhaps, than any man I know?
认识的人里我最喜欢你
You don't seek power
你不渴望权利
or popularity.
或者名气
You simply ask, is the thing right in itself?
你在乎的 是事物的本身是否正确
If it is, you do it, no matter the cost.
如果是 你会为此不计一切代价
That's all very well, Dumbledore
好吧差不多是这样 邓布利多
but, forgive me for asking, why can't you go?
但是请原谅 我想问 为什么你不去?
I cannot move against Grindelwald.
我不能对抗格林德沃
It has to be you.
只能是你
Well, I can't blame you,
好吧 我不怪你
in your shoes I'd probably refuse too.
如果我是你 我也很可能会拒绝
- What...? - It's late. Good evening, Newt
-什么... -不早了 晚安 纽特
Wait. No!
等等 不
Oh, come on.
哦 不会吧
Dumbledore.
邓布利多
Bunty!
邦缇
Bunty, the baby Nifflers are loose again!
邦缇 嗅嗅宝宝又跑出来了
Well done
好样的
I'm so sorry, Newt.
我很抱歉 纽特
They must have picked the lock while I was cleaning out the Augureys
他们肯定是趁我清理卜鸟的时候溜了
Not to worry.
没关系
I've fed nearly everyone, Pinky's had his nose drops, and
差不多都喂了 给平奇滴了鼻液 然后
And Elsie?
艾尔西呢
Elsie's droppings are nearly normal again.
艾尔西的粪便也快要正常了
Wonderful.
非常好
You can clock off now...
你现在可以下班了...
- I told you to leave the Kelpie to me. - That wound needs more ointment.
-我跟你说过把马形水怪交给我 -伤口还需要擦药膏
I don't want you losing fingers over it.
我不想你失去你的手指
Seriously, you go home now, Bunty.
说真的 快回去吧 邦缇
You must be exhausted.
你肯定累坏了
You know the Kelpie's easier with two.
两个人一起对付马形水怪会更容易
Perhaps you should take off your shirt?
要不要把衬衫脱了?
Don't worry,
别担心
I'll dry off quickly enough.
我马上就能弄干
Someone needed to let off some steam. Ointment, Bunty?
看起来有人需要宣泄一下感情 药膏 邦缇
You bite Bunty again and there'll be trouble, mister.
你再敢咬邦缇 我就要给你点颜色看看了 先生
What was that?
什么声音?
I don't know.
我不知道
But I want you to go home now, Bunty.
但是我想你真的该回家了 邦缇
Shall I call the Ministry?
需要我叫魔法部吗?
No, I want you to go home. Please.
不 我需要你回家 请回吧
If you could just give it to me...
如果可以 请把东西给我
Honey, if you could just give it to me.
亲爱的 麻烦把它给我
- He doesn't care. Hold it.
-他不会介意的 拿着
If you could just give it to me.
那就把它给我吧
Hey...
嘿...
NEWT! Get over here, you maniac.
纽特！到这里来 你这个小疯子
We hope you don't mind, Newt? We let ourselves in...
我们希望你不会介意 纽特 我们擅自进来了...
it's raining out there-cats and dogs!
外面在下雨 倾盆大雨
London's cold!
伦敦真冷
But you were supposed to have been Obliviated!
但是你不是应该一忘皆空了吗！
I know! It didn't work, pal.
我知道 但这没用 伙计
I mean, you said it, the potion only erases bad memories.
我是说 你说过 那个毒液只会消除不好的记忆
I didn't have any.
我压根儿没有
I mean, don't get me wrong, I had some weird ones...
别误会 我是有一些奇怪的记忆
but this angel...
但是这个天使...
this angel over here, she filled me in on all the bad parts.
这位天使把我遗忘的部分又重新告诉我了
And here we are, I guess, huh?
所以我们现在在这里了
This is wonderful!
这太棒了
Wait… is it…
等等 那是…
Tina? Tina?
蒂娜 蒂娜
Oh it's just us, honey.
哦 亲爱的 这里只有我们
Me and Jacob.
我和雅各布
Why don't I make us some dinner, huh?
你不介意我给大家做晚餐吧 嗯?
Yes!
好棒！
Hey, hon
嗨，甜心
Tina and I aren't talking.
蒂娜和我都不怎么说话了
Why?
为什么？
Oh well, you know, she found out about Jacob and
嗯...你知道 她发现了我和雅各布
I seeing each other and she didn't like it,
一直在见面 她不喜欢我们这样
cause of the “law.”
因为“法律”
Not allowed oops, not allowed to date No-Majs,
不许...不许和麻鸡约会
not allowed to marry them blah, blah, blah.
不许和他们结婚 没完没了
Well, she was all in a tizzy anyway, 'cause of you.
并且 因为你 她总是很容易感到烦躁
Me?
我？
Yeah, you, Newt
对 就你 纽特
It was in Spellbound
《意乱情迷》上都写了
Here, I brought it for you
在这 我替你带来了
Newt Scamander and fiancee Leta Lestrange
纽特·斯卡曼德和未婚妻莉塔·莱斯特兰奇
Brother Thesus and unknown woman
哥哥忒修斯的伴侣未知
No. So Thesus is marrying Leta, not me.
不 要娶莉塔的是忒修斯不是我
Oh. Oh dear.
哦天啊
Well,
但是
So Tina read that, and she started dating someone else
蒂娜看到消息后 就开始跟别人约会了
He’s an auror. His name is Achilles Tolliver
是个傲罗 叫阿喀琉斯·托利弗
Tolliver
托利佛
ANYWAY, we are really excited to be here Newt.
总之 我们来这里真的很高兴 纽特
This is a special trip for us.
这次旅行对我们来说很特别
You see, Jacob and I
雅各布和我
We’re getting married!
就要结婚啦
Marry Jacob
和雅各布结婚
You've enchanted him, haven't you?
你对他施法了是吗
What?
什么
I have not.
我没有
Will you stop reading my mind?
你能不能别读我心
Queenie, you've brought him here against his will.
奎妮 你违背他的意愿带他来这里的
Oh, that is an outrageous accusation. Look at him.
噢 你怎么能这么说 看看他
He's just happy.
他现在特别开心
Then you won't mind if I...
那你不会介意我
Please don't!
千万别
Queenie, you've got nothing to fear if he wants to get married.
奎妮 如果他想结婚的话你没什么好怕的
We can just lift the enchantment... and he can tell us himself.
我们可以让他恢复正常 然后自己告诉我们
What you got there?
你那是什么
Whatchu gonna do? Whatchu gonna do with that, Mr. Scamander?
你要干什么 你要用它干什么 斯卡曼德先生
Surgito.
咒术解除
Congratulations on your engagement, Jacob.
雅各布 恭喜你的订婚
Wait, what?
等等 什么
Oh no, you didn't.
哦不 你没有
Queen. A second.
奎儿 等下
Queenie!
奎妮
It's very nice to see you.
很高兴见到你
Where the hell am I right now?
我现在到底在哪里
Uh, uh, London.
额 伦敦
Oh! I always wanted to go here!
噢 我一直想来的
Queenie!
奎妮
Oh Queenie, honey.
噢 奎妮 亲爱的
Well, I'm just curious, when were you going to wake me up? After we'd had five kids?
等等 我只是想问一下 你准备什么时候让我恢复正常 当我们有了五个孩子以后吗
- Why is it wrong to want to marry you? - Okay.
-我想嫁给你有错吗 –好吧
To wanna have a family?
想要个家庭有错吗
I just want what everyone else has, that's all.
我只想拥有其他人有的东西 就这些
Okay, wait.. We talked about this, like, a million times.
好的 等等 我们都讨论过这个 快几百万次了
If we get married and they find out, they're gonna throw you in jail, sweetheart.
如果他们发现我们两个结婚的话 他们会把你扔进监狱的 亲爱的
I can't have that.
我不能让这发生
They don't like people like me marrying people like you.
他们不喜欢像我这样的人和像你这样的人通婚
I ain't a wizard. I'm just me.
我不是个巫师 只是个普通人
They're really progressive here, and they'll let us get married properly.
他们这边很包容 我们可以光明正大结婚的
Sweetheart, you don't need to enchant me.
亲爱的 你不需要对我施法
I'm already enchanted!
我早已为你着迷
I love you so much.
我太爱你了
- Yeah?? - Yeah.
-真的吗 -真的
But I can't have you risking everything like this, you know?
但我不能让你这样冒险 你知道吗
You're not giving us a choice, sweetheart.
你不给我任何选择 亲爱的
You're not givin' me a choice.
你也没有给我一个选择
One of us had to be brave, and you were being a coward!
我们两个必须有一个人需要勇敢起来 然后你还是个懦夫
I was being a coward?
我是个懦夫
If I'm a coward, you're...
如果我是个懦夫 你就是个
Crazy
疯子
I didn't say it...
我没这么说
- You didn't have to. - No, I didn't mean it, sweetheart.
-你不需要说出口 -我不是那个意思 亲爱的
Yeah, you did.
不 你就是那个意思
I'm gonna go see my sister.
我要去见我姐姐
Fine. See your sister. - Fine.
好 去见你姐姐去吧 - 好
No! Wait!
不，等等
Queenie! No! Queenie!
不，奎妮
I didn't mean it.
我不是这个意思
I didn't say nothing.
我什么也没说
恢复如初
Papyrus Reparo
PARIS
巴黎
My dear Queenie, what a beautiful city.
我亲爱的奎妮 这可真是个美丽的城市
I'm thinking of you. Tina.
我在想你 蒂娜
Hey, Newt?
嘿 纽特
Down here, Jacob. I'll be with you in a second.
在下面 雅各布 我马上过去
I got my own problems.
我自己的麻烦就不少了
BUNTY! DON'T FORGET TO GIVE PATRICK PELLETS.
邦缇 别忘了给帕特里克喂药
Tina Goldstein pointed as auror
（蒂娜·戈德斯坦恩成为傲罗）
Queenie left a postcard.
奎妮留下一张明信片
Tina's in Paris looking for Credence.
蒂娜在巴黎找克雷登斯
Genius!
太棒了
Queenie's gonna go straight for Tina.
奎妮会直接去找蒂娜的
Okay, we're going to France, pal!
好的 我们要去法国了 兄弟
- Hold on. I'll get my jacket. - I've got it
- 等下 我去拿我的夹克 - 我拿好了
Oh. Beautiful.
棒极了
删剪片段
Come on
来吧
I don't think it's reasonable to ask Bunty to cope with everyone here
我觉得叫邦缇应付这些生物和一堆新生儿
and a bunch of newborns, so...
不太合理，所以…
Are you insane?
你疯了吗?
You're gonna pack the nifflers now?
你现在要打包嗅嗅了吗?
- In you hop. - Remember what happened last time?
-进去吧 -记得上次发生什么事吗?
We fixed the lock.
我们把锁修好了
So nothing gets out without my say-so
现在没我允许什么都跑不出来
Come on.
快来吧
Get a move on.
快点啦
All right then. Accio necklace
行吧 项链飞来
Now you set a good example
现在你做个好榜样
BUNTY, GONE TO PARIS. HAVE TAKEN NIFFLERS WITH ME. NEWT.
（邦缇 我带了嗅嗅去巴黎 --纽特）
Nagini.
纳吉尼
Credence.
克雷登斯
I think I know where she is.
我想我知道她在哪里
We escape tonight.
我们今晚逃走
Hey.
嘿
I've told you to stay away from her, boy.
我跟你说过离她远点
Did I say you could take a break?
我说过你可以休息了吗
Clean out the Kappa.
去给河童洗澡
And you, get ready!
你 去做准备
Next in our little show of freaks and oddities...
接下来 我们这个精奇古怪的表演里
I present to you...
我要呈现给各位的
a Maledictus!
是一个血咒宿主
Once trapped in the jungles of Indonesia,
它曾经被困在印度尼西亚的森林里
she is the carrier of a blood curse.
身上背负着血咒
Such Under-beings are destined, through the course of their lives...
像她这样的生物 一生的宿命
to turn permanently into beasts.
注定是会永远转变成野兽的
But look at her.
看看她
So beautiful, yes?
多么漂亮 是不是
So desirable.
如此诱人
But soon she will be trapped forever in a very different body.
但是很快 她会永远被困在一副截然不同的躯体里了
Every night, when she sleeps, mesdames et messieurs...
每晚当她沉睡时，女士们和先生们
She is forced to become...
她都会变成...
Over time, she will not be able to transform back.
久而久之 她就再也变不回来了
She will be forever trapped in the body of a snake.
她会永远被困在蛇的躯体之中
Credence!
克雷登斯
Pack it up! Paris is done for us now.
收拾东西走人 巴黎容不下我们了
The boy with the Maledictus, what do you know about him?
关于和血咒宿主一起的男孩 你都了解些什么
He's looking for his mother.
他在找他的妈妈
All my freaks think they can go home.
我马戏团里所有的怪胎们觉得他们能回家
Okay, let's go.
好 走了
Look, I think we were both at the circus for the same reason, monsieur ...?
你看 我觉得我们是因为同一个原因来到马戏团的 先生
Kama. Yusuf Kama.
我是卡玛 尤瑟夫·卡玛
And you think right.
你想得没错
- What do you want with Credence? - The same as you.
-你想找克雷登斯干什么 -跟你一样的目的
Which is?
说说看
To prove who the boy really is.
证明他的真实身份
If the rumors of his identity are correct, he and I are
如果关于他身份的传言属实 那我们算是
distantly related.
远亲
I am the last male of my pure-blooded line.
我是我们纯血家族里的最后一名男丁
And so, if the rumors are correct, is he
若传闻属实 他也是我的族人
Have you read The Predictions of Tycho Dodonus?
你读过泰克 多多纳斯的预言录吗
Yeah. But that's poetry, not proof.
读过 但那只是诗 不能作为证据
If I could show you something better
我可以给你看看更充分
more concrete, something that proves who he is
更有说服力的证据 一些能证实他身份的东西
would the Ministries of Europe and America let him live?
欧洲和美国的魔法部会让他活下来吗
They might.
可能会
Then come.
那就跟我来吧
删剪片段
Oh no, Yaxley
又来了 亚克斯利
I hate the way he makes a beeline for me every time.
我讨厌他每次都这样直勾勾地盯着我
Not if you insist on being the most beautiful woman in the room.
没办法 谁让你一直都是屋子里最美的女人呢
It's not that and you know it.
你知道他不是这样想的
It's all blood with Yaxley.
亚克斯利的双手沾满了鲜血
Let me go and congratulate him and we can dance.
那我去祝贺他一下 我们就可以跳舞了
And then I promise I won't say a word to anyone for the rest of the night
而我保证在这以后今晚都不会跟任何人说一句话
- You promise? - Promise.
-你保证? -我保证
Sorry
抱歉
- How have you been? - You sly dog
-你最近怎么样 -你这只老狐狸
Is that her?
是她吗？
It is, look.
是的 你看
Her brother's alive
她弟弟还活着
The prediction is true
预言是真的
Her brother would lead us from the shadows
她弟弟会带领我们走出阴霾
”Return, great avenger, with wings from the water“
"回来吧 伟大的复仇者 带着水中之翼"
Congratulations, Leta
莉塔 恭喜你
Your brother lives
你弟弟活下来了
We all truly believe it
我们都十分相信这一点
So,
所以
Credence Barebone
克雷登斯 拜尔本
Nearly destroyed by the woman who raised him.
差点被他的养母毁掉
Yet now he seeks the mother who bore him.
但现在他在寻找他的生母
He's desperate for family.
他渴望家庭
He's desperate for love.
他渴望被爱
He's the key to our victory.
他是我们成功的关键
Well, we know where the boy is, don't we?
我们知道那个男孩在哪 不是吗
Why don't we grab him and leave!
为什么我们不抓了他就走
He must come to me freely，and he will.
他必须自愿来找我 而他也会这么做
The path has been laid, and he is following it.
路已经铺好了 他正在顺着它前进
The trail that will lead him to me,
这条路会把他带向我的身边
and the strange and glorious truth of who he is.
也会向他揭示他古怪而又光荣的身世
Why is he so important?
为什么他如此重要
Who represents the greatest threat to our cause?
谁代表着我们事业最大的威胁
Albus Dumbledore.
阿不思·邓布利多
If I asked you now to go to the school... where he is
如果我让你现在去学校 把他从藏身之处揪出来
hiding and kill him for me, would you do it for me, Krall?
替我杀了他 你愿意吗 克拉尔
Credence is the only entity alive...
克雷登斯是这世上唯一
who can kill him.
能杀死他的人
You really think that he can kill the great...
你真的认为他可以杀了伟大的...
can kill Albus Dumbledore?
可以杀了阿不思·邓布利多吗
I know he can.
我知道他可以
But will you be with us when that happens, Krall?
但克拉尔 当这一切发生时 你还会和我们站在一起吗
Will you?
会吗
删剪片段
What if she doesn't want me?
万一她不想要我呢
Make it happen.
好好照顾她吧
What?
什么
Because we are free.
因为我们自由了
Jacob, that man Tina's been seeing...
雅各布 那个蒂娜一直在约会的男人
Don't worry, she's gonna see you. And she'll see the four of us together
别担心 等她见到你 就会想起我们四个人一起的时光
it'll be just like New York all over again. Don't worry about it.
这就会像纽约那时一样 别担心
- Yes, but he's an Auror, Queenie said? - Yeah, he's an Auror. So what?
-是的 但奎妮说他是个傲罗 -是的 他是个傲罗 那又如何?
Don't worry about him.
别担心他
What do you think I should say to her, if I see her?
你觉得我见到她应该对她说什么
Oh, well, it's best not to plan these things.
哦，这个还是顺其自然吧
You know, you just say whatever comes to you in the moment.
你知道的 到时候你想到什么就说什么
She has eyes just like a salamander.
她的眼睛和火蜥蜴一样
Don't say that.
这还是算了
Nah, look, you just tell her that you missed her.
这样吧 你就直接告诉她你很想她
Right, and then you came all the way to Paris just to find her.
对 然后你大老远跑到巴黎就是为了找她
She'll love that. And then...
她会很开心的 然后
tell her you're losing sleep at night for thinking of her.
然后告诉她你想她想得失眠了
Just don't say anything about no salamanders, all right?
反正不要说任何关于火蜥蜴的事
Right. Okay.
好 行吧
Hey, hey, hey.
嘿 嘿
It's gonna be all right. We're in this together, pal.
一切都会好起来的 我们一起面对 兄弟
Okay, I'm gonna help you out. I'm gonna help you find Tina, find Queenie
好吧 我会帮你的 帮你找到蒂娜和奎妮
and we'll all be happy again. Just like old times.
然后我们就会像往日一样开心了
Who is this guy?
那个人是谁
He's the only way I can leave the country without documentation.
他是我不经允许离开这个国家的唯一途径
Now, you don't suffer from motion sickness, do you?
你不会晕船吧?
I don't do well on boats, Newt.
纽特 我并不是很适应坐船
You'll be fine.
不会有事的
Stir your stumps-it leaves in one minute!
赶快 一分钟后出发
Fifty Galleons.
50加隆
No, we said thirty.
不，我们说好30的
Thirty to go to France,
30是去法国的路费
twenty not to tell anyone, I seen Newt Scamander leaving the country illegally.
另外20是封口费 不把纽特·斯卡曼德非法离境的事情说出去
Price of fame, pal.
名声的代价啊 兄弟
Ten seconds.
10秒
Eight.
八
Jacob.
雅各布
Seven.
七
Six.
六
Four. Three. Two.
四、三、二
One.
一
I didn't like that Portkey, Newt.
我不喜欢那个门钥匙 纽特
So you keep saying. Follow me.
你老这么说 跟着我
Confundus.
混淆视听
Come on. That'll wear off in a few minutes.
来吧 咒语几分钟就失效了
Appare vestigium.
踪迹显形
Accio Niffler...
嗅嗅飞来
Get looking. Oi! Get looking.
快去找 喂 快去找
That's a Kappa, That's a Japanese water demon.
那是河童 是个日本水怪
Tina?
蒂娜
What have you found?
你找到了什么
And we're licking the dirt now.
还要吃土的吗
Revelio.
原形立现
Newt... what made those?
纽特 这是什么
That is a Zouwu.
那是驺吾
It's a Chinese creature. They are incredibly fast and incredibly powerful.
是中国的一种神兽 速度极快且力量强大
They can travel a thousand miles in a day
能够日行千里
and this one could take you from one part of Paris to the next in a single leap.
一步就能跨越整座巴黎城
Oh, good boy.
哦 真棒
Jacob, she was here.
雅各布 她来过
Tina stood here.
蒂娜在这里待过
She has incredibly narrow feet, have you noticed?
你注意到了吗 她的脚特别细
Can't say that I have.
我还真没在意
Then someone came towards her.
然后有人走向了她
Avenseguim.
(追踪咒)
- Follow that feather. - What?
-跟着那片羽毛 -什么
- Jacob, follow the feather. - Follow the feather.
-雅各布 跟着羽毛 -跟着羽毛
Where is he?
它在哪
Accio Niffler.
嗅嗅飞来
Let go of the bucket!
别提着桶了
I'm sorry, I don't know what you just said at all.
对不起 我听不懂
Welcome to the French Ministry of Magic.
欢迎来到法国魔法部
What is your business, please?
请问有何贵干
I need to speak to Tina Goldstein.
我要找蒂娜·戈德斯坦恩
She's an American Auror working on a case here.
她是个美国傲罗 在这里办案
We have no Tina Goldstein here.
这里没有蒂娜·戈德斯坦恩
No, it's... I'm sorry there must be some sort of mistake.
不可能的 对不起 一定是哪里弄错了
See, I know she's in Paris, she sent me a postcard.
我知道她在巴黎 还给我寄了一张明信片
I brought it, I can show it to you. Maybe you can help me find her here?
我带来了 你看你能不能帮我找她
It's just in here.
就在这里
Oh rabbits! If you can just wait one moment!
该死 麻烦你等一下
I know it's in here somewhere. I definitely packed it.
就在我包里 我肯定收起来了
Where?
放哪了
One second.
等一下
- Could we at least stop for a coffee, or like a... - Not now, Jacob.
- 我们能不能至少停下来喝杯咖啡 或者… - 雅各布 还不是时候
Chocolate or... just for a second
或是热巧克力 一下就好
This way. Come on.
走这边 快点
Pain Au chocolat? Half a croissant, or like, a bonbon?
(法语)巧克力面包要吗 半块羊角面包或者糖果
This way.
这边
Jacob!
雅各布
Jacob?
Madame?
(法语)女士
(法语)你还好吗 女士
删剪片段
She’s home.
她在家
Qui est là?
(法语)是谁啊
C’est votre fils, madame.
(法语) 您的儿子来了 夫人
Qui est-ce?
(法语) 你是谁
Are you Irma?
你是厄玛吗
Are you Irma Dugart?
你是…你是厄玛·杜加尔德吗
I’m sorry. Your name is on my adoption paper.
抱歉 我的领养文件上写的是你的名字
Does this make sense?
能想起什么吗
You gave me to Mrs. Bareborn in New York.
你把我交给纽约的拜尔伯恩太太了
I’m not your mother. I am just a servant.
我不是你妈妈 我只是个仆人
You were a so beautiful baby.
你那时是个漂亮娃娃
And you are a beautiful man.
现在长成帅小伙了
I didn’t want to leave you there.
我没想把你留在那儿
Why didn’t they want me?
他们为什么不想要我
Why is your name on my adoption paper?
为什么我的领养文件上是你的名字
I took you to Mrs. Bareborn
我带你去拜尔本太太那儿
because she was supposed to look after you.
想着她能照顾你
She’s dead.
她死了
How did the boy take it?
那男孩反应如何？
He’s sensitive.
他很敏感
The ministry won’t be happy when I tell them I missed.
魔法部知道我失手了 一定不会高兴的
-I know my reputation.
-我清楚我的名声
Listen to me. The disapproval of cowards is praise to the brave.
听我说 懦夫的反对是对勇者的赞扬
Your name will be written in glory when wizards rule the world.
当巫师统治世界 你的姓名将伴随荣光
And the clock is ticking faster.
这一天不会远了
Watch over Credence. Keep him safe.
照顾好克雷登斯 确保他安全
For the Greater Good.
为了更伟大的利益
You know what I miss about Queenie?
你知道我想念奎妮什么吗
Everything.
一切
I even miss the stuff that drove me nuts.
我甚至怀念那些让我发疯的东西
Like the mind reading.
比如读心术
I was happy to have someone like her even interested in…
她那样的人竟然会对我感兴趣…
Anything I thought.
我觉得很幸福
You know what I mean?
你明白我的意思吗
Sorry?
你说啥
I was saying… You’re sure the guy is here we’re looking for?
我是说 你确定我们要找的人就在这里?
Definitely. The feather said so.
肯定没错 羽毛是这么指示的
-Is that the guy we’re looking for? –Yes.
-那就是我们要找的人吗? -是的
Sorry.
抱歉
Bonjour… Bonjour, monsieur.
(法语)您好… 您好 先生
Wait, no, sorry
等等，抱歉
We were just wondering if you came across a friend of ours.
我们只是想知道你是否遇到过我们的一个朋友…
Tina Goldstein.
蒂娜·戈德斯坦恩
Messieurs, Paris is a large city.
先生们 巴黎可是座大城市
She’s an auror.
她是个傲罗
When an auror goes missing the Ministry tends to come looking, so…
傲罗失踪的话魔法部会来找人 所以…
I suppose it would probably be better if we reported her absence.
我想我们还是回去上报失踪人口算了
Is she tall? Dark?
她个子高吗 皮肤黑吗
Rather…
是不是比较…
-Serious. –Beautiful.
-很严肃 –很漂亮
Yeah, what I meant to say was she’s very—very pretty.
我想说的是 她非常--非常漂亮
I think I saw someone like this last night.
我想我昨晚见过这样的人
Perhaps if I showed you where?
也许我可以带你们去找她
If you don’t mind that would be…
如果你不介意的话...
-That would be lovely. –Sure.
-那太好了 –请随我来
Tina?
蒂娜
Newt!
纽特
Expelliarmus
除你武器
My apologies, Mr. Scamander.
对不起 斯卡曼德先生
I shall return and release you once Credence is dead.
克雷登斯一死 我就回来放你们出去
Kama, wait!
卡玛，等等！
You see, whether he dies, or I do.
不是他死 就是我亡
Oh, no.
不不不
No, no, no--
哦不不不
Well, that was not the best out for a rescue attempt.
营救任务进行得可不太顺利
Oh this was a rescue attempt? You just lost me my only lead.
这是一次营救行动吗 你刚刚害我丢掉唯一的线索
Well, how was the interrogation going before we turned up?
好吧 在我们出现前审讯怎么样
Newt!
纽特
Well done, Pick.
干得好 皮克
You said you needed this man?
你说你需要这个人?
Yes. I think this man knows where Credence is, Mr. Scamander.
对 我想这个人知道克雷登斯在哪里 斯卡曼德先生
Well, that'll be the Zouwu.
那一定就是驺吾了
Come on, Newt, get out of there!
来啊 纽特 快离开那儿
Come on
走了
What were the three biggest mistakes that you made last time?
你上次犯的最大的三个错误是什么?
Caught by surprise, sir.
被突袭而措手不及 先生
What else?
还有呢
Didn't parry before counter-curse, sir.
是在破解咒前没有回避 老师
Very good. And the last one...
很好 那最后一个...
the most important one?
最重要的那个错误是什么?
Not learning from the first two.
没从前两个错误里学到教训
This is a school, you've no right
这里是学校 你们无权闯入
I'm the Head of Magical Law Enforcement and I have the right to go wherever I please.
我是魔法法律执行司的司长 我想去哪里都可以
Out of here.
你们出去
Go with Professor McGonagall, please.
你们和麦格教授一起出去吧
He's the best teacher we've got.
他是我们最好的老师
- Thanks, McClaggan. - Get out!
-谢谢你 麦克拉根 -出去
Come, McClaggan.
走吧 麦克拉根
Newt Scamander is in Paris.
纽特·斯卡曼德现在在巴黎
Really?
真的吗
Cut the pretense. I know he's there on your orders.
少装了 我知道他是奉你之命去的
If you'd ever had the pleasure to teach him, you'd
如果你有幸教过纽特
know Newt is not a great follower of orders.
你就会知道他不是个会乖乖听话的孩子
You've read The Predictions of Tycho Dodonus??
你读过泰克 多多纳斯的预言录吗
Mmm. Many years ago.
多年前读过
"A son cruelly banished. Despair of the daughter."
“被残忍放逐之子 伤心且绝望之女”
- "Return..." - Yes, I know it.
-“伟大…” -我知道预言
There's a rumor this prediction refers to the Obscurial.
有谣言说这个预言指的是默然者
他们说格林德沃想要…
They say that Grindelwald wants...
As a highborn henchman. I've heard the rumor.
一个出身名门的亲信 我听过传闻
And yet, Scamander appears wherever the Obscurial goes,
但无论默然者在哪现身 斯卡曼德都会及时出现
to protect him.
去保护他
Meanwhile, you've built up quite the little network of international contacts.
在此同时 你也结交了不少的国际友人
However long you keep me and my friends under surveillance,
不管你想监视我和我朋友多久
you're not going to discover plots against you, Travers,
都不会发现我们有任何地方违背你 特拉弗斯
because we want the same thing. The defeat of Grindelwald.
因为我们想要的是一样的 就是去打败格林德沃
But I warn you, your policies of suppression and violence
但我警告你 运用镇压和暴力的手段
are pushing supporters into his arms.
只会把人逼到他那一方去
I'm not interested in your warnings.
我对你的警告不感兴趣
Now...
现在
It pains me to say it because I don't like you...
我不想这么说 因为我不喜欢你
但…
But...
能与他抗衡的巫师只有你
You are the only wizard who is his equal.
我需要你去对抗他
I need you to fight him.
I can't.
我做不到
是因为这个吗？
Because of this?
You and Grindelwald were as close as brothers.
你与格林德沃曾经亲如兄弟
Oh, we were closer than brothers.
我们比亲兄弟还亲
Will you fight him?
你愿意对抗他吗?
I can't.
我不能
Well, then you have chosen your side.
那你已经选好你的立场了
From now on, I shall know every spell you cast.
从现在起 我将知道你念的每一个咒语
I'm doubling the watch on you,
我会派双倍人马监视你
and you will no longer teach Defense Against the Dark Arts.
你也不再能教黑魔法防御术了
Where's Leta? We need to go to Paris.
莉塔在哪？我们得赶往巴黎
Theseus.
忒修斯
忒修斯 若格林德沃召集大型集会
Theseus, if Grindelwald calls a rally,
don't try and break it up.
别试图去破坏
Don't let Travers send you in there.
别让特弗拉斯把你派进去
若你曾相信过我…
If you ever trusted me...
Theseus.
忒修斯
Theseus!
Even the name Lestrange makes me feel sick.
光想到莱斯特兰奇这个姓就让我恶心
You know she stays here every vacation.
你也知道她每次放假都留在学校
Her family don't actually want her home.
她家人根本不希望她回家
I don't blame them. She's so annoying.
也不怪他们 她实在太讨人厌
Did you see her last week?
你上个礼拜看到她了吗
Oscausi!
闭而不语
Professor McGonagall!
麦格教授
Lestrange has done it again!
莱斯特兰奇又违反校规了
Lestrange, stop running!
莱斯特兰奇 别跑
- Lestrange! Disobedient children. - Leta, come back!
-莱斯特兰奇！不听话的孩子！快停下！ -莉塔 回来
Stop! Shame on the House of Slytherin.
别跑了 真让斯莱特林学院蒙羞
A hundred points! Two hundred!
扣一百分 扣两百分
Get back here, right now!
给我回来 立马
Children, stop it! You, stop! Come back!
孩子们 停下来！你 停下来！回来！
- Out of my way! - Where has she gone?
-别挡路 -她去哪了？
I think she went that way!
我想她往那边去了
Miss, it was Lestrange. She's horrible.
老师 是莱斯特兰奇干的！她最坏了！
Scamander, why aren't you packing?
斯卡曼德 你为什么不收拾行李
I'm not going home.
我不回家
Why not?
为什么
He needs me.
它需要我
He was hurt.
它受伤了
What is that?
那是什么
A raven chick.
一只小渡鸦
Isn't the raven your family emblem?
渡鸦不是你家族的标志么
Yes, it is.
对 没错
All right, Newt.
好了 纽特
Be brave.
勇敢一点
That's an unusual one.
真是不同寻常
So Mr. Scamander fears what more than anything else in the world?
所以斯卡曼德先生 在人生中最畏惧的是
被困在办公室里工作 老师
Having to work in an office, sir.
Go ahead, Newt.
继续 纽特
Riddikulus.
滑稽滑稽
漂亮
Well done.
Good job. Leta.
干得好 莉塔
It's only a Boggart.
就是一只博格特
It can't hurt you.
它伤害不了你
Everyone is scared of something.
每个人都有害怕的东西
I've been looking forward to this.
我一直很期待这一刻
I don't want to talk about it.
我不想谈那件事
They know me,
它们认识我
or they'd hide.
不然会躲起来
They only nest in trees with wand-quality wood.
它们只在木质能制成魔杖的树上筑巢
你知道吗
Did you know that?
And they have very complex social lives.
它们也有很复杂的社交生活
If you watch them for long enough, you realize...
要是你观察得够久 就会发现的…
Hello, Leta. This is a surprise.
嗨，莉塔，真让人讶异
Finding me in a classroom?
会在教室里看到我?
Was I such a bad student?
我是坏学生吗?
On the contrary, you were one of my cleverest.
恰恰相反 你是我最聪明的学生之一
I said "bad," not "stupid."
我说坏学生 不是笨学生
别费心回答了
Don't bother answering.
我知道你没喜欢过我
I know you never liked me.
You're wrong.
那你错了
我从不认为你坏
I never thought you bad.
You were alone, then. Everybody else did.
那你是个例外 所有人都这么觉得
而且他们是对的
And they were right.
我的确很坏
I was wicked.
Leta, I know how painful
莉塔 我了解那些
the rumors about your brother Corvus must be for you.
关于你弟弟考乌斯的谣言 令你有多痛苦
No, you don't.
不 你不了解
Not unless you had a brother who died, too.
除非你也有个死去的弟弟
In my case, it was my sister.
我妹妹不在了
Did you love her?
你爱她吗
我应该更爱她的
Not as well as I should have done.
Never too late to free yourself.
让自己释怀是从来不会晚
有人说 忏悔是一种解脱 能让你如释重负
Confession is a relief, I'm told. A great weight lifted.
多年来悔恨一直伴随着我
Regret is my constant companion.
Do not let it become yours.
别让它也变成你的心魔
Oh! No, thank you.
不用了 谢谢
Well...
好了
You've been really kind,
你人实在太好了
but my sister Tina's probably worried sick about me.
我姐姐蒂娜大概急着找我找疯了
You know, banging on all the doors and things,
像是到处乱敲门之类的
我还是走好了
so I think I'd better be going.
But you haven't met your host.
但你还没见到主人
Oh, are you married?
噢 你结婚了?
应该说…
Let's say,
deeply committed.
我完全效忠于他
You see, I can't tell if you're making a joke or if you're just...
你看我就是分不清你到底是开玩笑还是…
French.
法国人都这样
Oh.
噢
Hey, knock it off.
喂 别闹了
You stay right there.
你别过来
I know what you are.
我知道你是谁
Queenie.
奎妮
We are not here to hurt you.
我们不是来伤害你的
We only want to help you.
我们只想帮助你
You're so very, very far away from home.
你离家太远了
Far away from everything you love, everything that is comfortable.
远离一切你所深爱的事物 远离你的舒适圈
I would never see you harmed.
我不想看你受伤害
Ever.
永远不想
It is not your fault that your sister is an Auror.
你姐姐是一名傲罗并不是你的错
I wish you were working with me now
我希望你现在能与我同一阵线
towards a world where we wizards were free to live openly.
努力让世界能容许巫师光明正大的生活
能择其所爱
To love freely.
You are an innocent.
你从未伤害任何人
So go now.
你走吧
离开这地方
Leave this place.
删剪片段
原来你在这
There you are.
What did Travers want? Absolutely outrageous behavior.
特拉弗斯到底想干什么? 他的行为太过分了
Marching into a school like that.
那样冲进一所学校
It was all very mundane,
那不算什么
I'm fine, sorry, Minerva, lot of marking.
不好意思 米勒娃 我还有很多作业要批改
Hey, uh, Newt, buddy. Uh...
嘿纽特 兄弟 额……
Tina's up here. She's all by her lonesome,
蒂娜在上面 她就孤单一人
and, uh, maybe you want to come up and keep her company?
所以你要不要上来陪陪她?
Uh, I've been looking for food, and I ain't found any,
我四处找食物可一直都没找到
so I guess I'm gonna go upstairs and try my luck
所以我觉得我要上楼碰碰运气
in, oh, I don't know, the attic.
或许阁楼也得看看
You're all right.
你会没事的
Relashio.
力劲松懈
Okay.
好吧
She's responded well to the Dittany.
它对白鲜的反应很好
She was born to run, you see.
它天生就爱乱跑
But I think she's...She's just lacking in confidence.
但我想它只是有点缺乏自信
Mr. Scamander, have you got anything in your case
斯卡曼德先生 你皮箱里有东西
that might help revive this man?
能叫醒这个人吗
I need to question him.
我得盘问他
I think he knows who Credence really is. And the scars on his hand
我想他知道克雷登斯的真实身份 而他手上的伤疤
- suggest an Unbreakable Vow. - An Unbreakable Vow.
-代表他曾立下牢不可破咒 -牢不可破咒
Yeah, I noticed that, too.
我也注意到了
Lumos.
荧光闪烁
What was that?
那是什么?
There must be a Water Dragon in that sewer.
那个下水道里一定有水龙
它们身上常常有这种寄生虫 你看 它们…
They carry these parasites, you see. They, um...
- Jacob. - Yeah?
-雅各布 -咋了
In my case, in the pocket there, you'll find a pair of tweezers.
在我皮箱的夹层中，有一支镊子
Tweezers?
镊子?
-就是细细尖尖… -尖尖的工具
- They're thin, pointy... - Little pointy things.
Yes, I know what tweezers are.
我知道镊子是什么
All right. You might not want to watch this.
你应该不会想看这个场面的
I can handle it.
我没问题
Come out.
出来吧
Come on. You're all right.
来吧 你没事
- Ew. - Come on. I got you.
来啊 我拉住了
Jacob, will you take that for me?
雅各布 能帮我拿着吗
Calamari.
透抽
Must kill him.
一定要杀了他
Who?
谁
Credence?
克雷登斯?
It may take him a few hours to recover.
可能要几小时才会恢复
That parasite's poison is quite strong.
那寄生虫的毒性颇强
我必须回魔法部去汇报进度
I have to go back to the Ministry with what I've got.
It's nice to see you again, Mr. Scamander.
很高兴再次见到你 斯卡曼德先生
Hey. Hey . Hold on a second, will ya?
唉唉 稍等一下 好吗
Hold on. Hold on.
稍等 等一下
Wait! Tina.
别走蒂娜
You didn't mention salamanders, did you?
你没提火蜥蜴吧?
我没有 她就这样走了 我不懂
No, I didn't. She just ran. I don't know...
So you chase after her.
你要去追啊
蒂娜 拜托你听我说
Tina. Please, just listen to me.
斯卡曼德 我得去跟魔法部汇报
Mr. Scamander, I need to go talk to the Ministry.
我知道你对于傲罗的看法
I know how you feel about Aurors.
I may have been a little strong
我在那些信里的言辞可能有一些过激
in the way that I expressed myself in that letter.
What was the exact phrase? "A bunch of careerist hypocrites"?
你用的是什么词来着? 一群虚伪又野心勃勃的人
I'm sorry, but I can't admire people
很抱歉 我不欣赏那些
whose answer to everything that they fear or misunderstand is "kill it."
对于一切不了解或者恐惧的东西就起了杀心的人
I'm an Auror and I don't.
我就是一名傲罗 然而我并不是那样的人
Yes, I know. That's because you've gone middle head.
是的 因为你是中间那个头
Excuse me?
你说什么?
It's an expression derived from the three heads of the Runespoor.
这个措辞来自如尼纹蛇的三个头
So the middle one is the visionary.
中间那个头最有远见
Now, every Auror in Europe wants Credence dead, except you.
除你以外整个欧洲的傲罗都想要格雷登斯死
You've gone middle head.
所以你是中间那个头
Who else uses that expression, Mr. Scamander?
还有谁会用这种表述吗 斯卡曼德先生
I think it might just be me.
大概只有我会用吧
是格林德沃 他在召集他的追随者
It's Grindelwald. He's calling his followers.
It's too late. Grindelwald has come for Credence.
太迟了 格林德沃是冲着格雷登斯来的
- He might already have him. - It's not too late.
-搞不好已经找到他了 -还不算迟
We can still get to him first.
我们还是能先找到他
你要去哪
Where are you going?
The French Ministry of Magic.
法国魔法部
That's the last place Credence would go.
克雷登斯最不可能去那里了
魔法部里藏有一个盒子
There's a box hidden in the Ministry, Tina.
It's a box that can tell us who Credence really is.
它能告诉我们克雷登斯的真实身份
A box? What are you talking about?
盒子? 你在讲什么?
Trust me.
相信我
你想出来吗? 就一小会儿
You wanna come out, just for a little while?
You can be free.
可以自由走动
Credence.
克雷登斯
What do you want?
你想要什么?
From you?
从你身上?
Nothing.
什么也不要
我能给你什么?
For you?
Everything I never had.
我未曾拥有的一切
But what is it you want, my boy?
但你又想要什么 孩子?
I want to know who I am.
我想知道我究竟是谁
This is where you will find proof of your true identity.
你会在这里找到你真实身份的证据
Come to Père Lachaise tonight, and you will discover the truth.
今晚到拉雪兹神父公墓 你会知道事实
Father, why did you make me...
父亲 你为何要逼我
等等
Wait...
Wait.
等等
我恐怕这屋子里没什么吃的
I'm afraid we keep no food in the house.
Are you a ghost?
你是鬼吗?
No.
不
No. I'm alive.
不 我是活人
But I'm an alchemist and therefore immortal.
但我是炼金术士 所以长生不老
You don't look a day over 375.
你看起来绝对不超过375岁
很抱歉我们没有敲门
I'm sorry that we didn't knock.
No. No matter.
不 没关系
Albus told me some friends might be dropping in.
阿不思有跟我说会有朋友造访
Nicolas Flamel.
我是尼可•勒梅
Jacob Kowalski.
我是雅各布·科沃斯基
I'm sorry.
对不起
It's all right.
没关系
- I didn't... - Oh... Oh!
-我不是… -哦 哦
At last, we see some development.
终于有些动静了
Yeah. I've seen one of these before.
对 我以前看过这个东西
It was at the fair.
是在园游会
有个戴面纱的女人
There was this dame there, and she had a veil,
and I gave her a nickel, and she told me about my future.
我给她五分钱 然后她预言我的未来
And she missed out on quite a bit, actually.
其实她漏掉好多东西
Wait a minute, I know him. That's the kid. That's Credence.
等等 我认识他 是克雷登斯那小子
老天
Jeez.
Hey... Hey!
嘿
That's Queenie. There she is. Hi, baby.
那是奎妮 她在那儿 嗨 宝贝
Where is this? Is this here?
这是哪 是不是在这附近?
Yes. This is the Lestrange tomb.
是的 这是莱斯特兰奇家族的墓
It lies in the cemetery of Père Lachaise.
坐落在拉雪兹神父公墓内
我来了 宝贝 别走开
I'm coming, baby. Stay right there.
谢谢你 勒梅先生
Thank you, Mr. Flamel.
- Ouch. - I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Okay.
-啊！-哦 对不起 对不起 好吧
Oh, look after Mr. Tentacles for me. Oh, no.
帮我顾一下章鱼哥 哦不
I'm sorry. I gotta go.
抱歉 我得走了
Please, you mustn't go to the cemetery.
请你千万不能去公墓
What's happening?
发生什么事了?
Exactly what he said would happen.
完全照他说的发生了
Grindelwald rallies at the cemetery tonight,
格林德沃今晚会在公墓集会
and there will be death.
肯定会有伤亡
Then you gotta go.
那你得过去
What? I haven't seen action in 200 years.
什么 我已经两百年没动过手了
Flamel, you can do this. We believe in you.
勒梅 你必须得去 我们对你有信心
The box is in the Ancestral Records room, Tina.
盒子在族谱档案室里 蒂娜
So it's three floors down.
所以 应该在地下三楼
Is that Polyjuice?
那是复方汤剂吗
It's just enough to get me inside.
这些只够我混进去
- Who... - It's my brother, Theseus.
-是谁... -我哥哥 忒修斯
他是个傲罗 还很爱抱人
He's an Auror and a hugger.
What's happening?
怎么了
Grindelwald's rallying.
格林德沃要举行集会
We don't know where, but we think it's tonight.
地点不知道 但估计是今晚
- Be careful. - Of course.
-小心点 -当然
- Promise me you'll be careful. - Of course. I'm gonna be careful.
-答应我要你一定要小心 -我当然会小心的
Listen, I want you to hear this from me.
听好 我希望是由我告诉你
They think that Credence boy might be your missing brother.
他们认为克雷登斯 可能是你失踪的弟弟
- My brother is dead. - I know.
-我弟弟已经死了 -我知道
- He died. - I know.
-他死了 -我知道
- How many times, Theseus? - And the records will prove that.
-这话还要说几次 忒修斯? -档案会证明一切
- Okay? They can't lie. - Theseus.
-好吗 档案不会说谎 -忒修斯
I want every person at that rally arrested. If they resist...
我要你逮捕参与集会的每一人 若反抗…
Sir, forgive me, but if we go in too heavy,
长官 如果我们逼得太紧
- don't we run the risk of adding to... - Just do it.
-不就助长了… -照做就行了
我猜你无法在法国魔法部内幻影移形吧?
I don't suppose you can Disapparate on Ministry premises in France, can you?
Nope.
不行
Pity.
真可惜
-纽特 -是 我知道 我知道
- Newt! - Yes, I know. I know it's...
Newt!
纽特
- Oh! - That's your brother?
那个是你哥哥?
So I think I may have mentioned in my letters
我想我在信中提过
that we have quite a complicated relationship.
我们俩的关系很复杂
Newt, stop!
纽特 停下来
- Does he wanna kill you? - Frequently.
-他想杀你吗? -经常
Enough!
别跑了
他需要控制他的脾气
He needs to control his temper.
我觉得这可能是我此生最棒的时刻
I think that might have been the best moment of my life.
Queenie.
奎妮
Queenie, honey.
奎妮 甜心
Don't. Don't move.
别 别动
有何贵干?
Yes, this is Leta Lestrange.
这位是莉塔·莱斯特兰奇
我是她的…
And, uh, I'm her...
未婚夫
Fiancé.
进去吧
Thank you.
谢谢
Tina, about that fiancée business...
蒂娜 关于未婚夫那件事
Oh, sorry. Yeah, I should have congratulated you.
抱歉 我该恭喜你
- No, that's... - Lumos.
-不 那是… -荧光闪烁
莱斯特兰奇
Lestrange.
Tina, about Leta...
蒂娜 关于莉塔
Yes, I've just said I am happy for you.
是的 我说了替你开心
No, I don't... Please, don't be happy.
我没有 拜托别不开心
No. Sorry. I don't...
不 抱歉 我不是…
Obviously, I...
很显然我…
Obviously, I want you to be...
很显然我希望你开心
And I hear that you are now. Which is wonderful.
我也听说你现在很开心 那很棒
Sorry, what I'm trying to say is, I want you to be happy,
抱歉 我想说的是 我希望你开心
but I don't want you to be happy that I'm happy, because I'm not.
但我不想你因为我开心而开心 因为我没有…
Happy.
开心
Or engaged.
或是订婚
- What? - It was a mistake in a stupid magazine.
-什么? -那本蠢杂志搞错了
My brother's marrying Leta, June the 6th.
是我哥要娶莉塔 婚期定在六月六号
I'm supposed to be best man,
我是伴郎
which is sort of mildly hilarious.
说起来有点可笑
Does he think you're here to win her back?
他认为你是来横刀夺爱的吗
Are you here to win her back?
你是来横刀夺爱的吗
No, I'm here...
不 我来这里…
You know, your eyes really are...
你知道 你的眼睛真的…
真的什么?
Are what?
有人叫我不要说
I'm not supposed to say.
-我剪下你的照片 -纽特 我读了你的书
- I cut a picture of you... - Newt, I read your book and...
- Wait, did you read... - Did you?
-等等 你读了... -你有吗?
I cut this, um...
我把这剪下
It's just a picture of you from the paper,
就是报纸上面你的照片
很有趣 因为在报纸上你的眼睛…
but it's interesting 'cause your eyes in newsprint...
See, in reality they have this effect in them, Tina. It's like...
看你本人时 你眼睛里有种光辉 就像...
像是黑水中燃烧的火焰
It's like fire in water, in dark water.
And I've only ever seen that...
我只曾在动物身上见过
I've only ever seen that in...
我只曾在动物身上见过 那就是…
火蜥蜴
Salamanders.
Come.
来
Lestrange.
莱斯特兰奇
资料移至拉雪兹神父公墓内的 莱斯特兰奇家族陵墓
Circumrota.
即刻旋转
Hello, Newt.
你好 纽特
Hello, Leta.
你好 莉塔
Hi.
嗨
Oh, no.
哦不
What kind of cats are those?
那是什么猫？
Uh, these aren't cats.
那些不是猫
They're Matagots. They're spirit familiars.
是玛达戈猫 一种灵性生物
它们守卫魔法部
They guard the Ministry.
But they won't hurt you unless you...
它们不会伤人 除非…
昏昏倒地
Stupefy!
Unless you attack them.
除非你先攻击它们
Oops.
糟糕
-莉塔 -通通复原
- Leta. - Reverte.
Accio!
速速飞来
Ascendio!
齐齐高攀
Okay. Wait. Hold it there, please.
等等 别闹了等一下 拜托
Come on.
别这样
All right.
好了
Okay, wait.
好了 等等
You, go back. Move! Out of the way!
你，退后，快点，快让开
If I must kill you as well as Corvus, I shall.
若杀考乌斯也得杀了你 我会动手
Stop!
住手
Yusuf.
尤瑟夫
真的是你吗
Is that really you?
我的妹妹?
My little sister?
所以他是你哥哥
So he's your brother.
Who am I?
我是谁?
I don't know.
我不知道
I'm tired of living with no name and no history.
我厌倦了无名无过往的人生
Just tell me my story, then you can end it.
跟我说我的故事 之后任凭处置
Your story is our story.
你的故事就是我们的故事
- Our story.
我们的故事
- No, Yusuf.
不 尤瑟夫
My father was Mustafa Kama.
我父亲穆斯塔法·卡玛
Pure-blood of Senegalese descent and most accomplished.
是塞内加尔裔最知名的纯血巫师
My mother, Laurena,
我母亲劳瑞娜
was equally highbred, a noted beauty.
同样是出身名门的著名美女
They were deeply in love.
他们深爱彼此
They knew a man of great influence from a famous French pure-blood family.
他俩认识一名出身法国纯血望族的男人
He desired her.
他贪恋她的美色
Maman. Maman!
(法语)妈妈
Lestrange used the Imperius Curse to seduce and abduct her.
莱斯特兰奇用夺魂咒勾引并绑架她
I tried to prevent it, but he attacked me.
我试着阻止 但他攻击了我
That was the last time I ever saw her.
那是我最后一次看到她
She died giving birth to a little girl.
她生下一名女婴 难产而死
You.
就是你
The news of her death drove my father insane.
她的死讯把我父亲逼疯
With his dying breath,
在咽下最后一口气前
my father charged me to seek revenge.
我父亲要我为他复仇
Kill the person Lestrange loves best in the world.
杀死莱斯特兰奇世上最爱的人
I thought at first it'd be easy.
我一开始以为很容易
He had only one close relative.
他只有一个近亲
You.
就是你
But he...
但是他…
Say it.
说吧
He never loved you.
他从没爱过你
He remarried, and not three months after her death.
她死后不足三个月 他就再婚了
He loved her no more than he had loved you.
他既不爱她 也不爱你
But then his son, Corvus, was born at last.
但他的儿子考乌斯随后出生
And that man who had never known love was filled with it.
那个从不知爱为何物的人 突然充满父爱
All he cared about
他唯一在乎的
was little Corvus.
只有小考乌斯
So this is the truth?
所以是真的?
I am Corvus Lestrange?
我是考乌斯·莱斯特兰奇?
- Yes. Yes. - No. No.
-对 -不对
Realizing that Mustafa Kama's son had sworn revenge,
知道穆斯塔法·卡玛之子 立誓报仇后
你父亲要把你藏在我找不到的地方
your father sought to hide you where I couldn't find you.
So he confided you to his servant, who boarded a ship for America.
他将你托付给仆人 搭船前往美国
- He did send Corvus to America, but... - His servant, Irma Dugard,
-他的确送考乌斯去美国 但… -他的仆人伊尔玛·杜加尔德
was a half-elf.
是个混血精灵
Her magic was weak,
她的法力太弱
and therefore left no trace I could follow.
留下的踪迹让我无法追踪
I had only just discovered how you had escaped
我终于发现你如何逃脱时
when I received news I never expected.
我收到出乎意料外的消息
The ship had gone down at sea.
船在大海中沉没了
但你幸存下来了 不是吗?
But you survived, didn't you?
Somehow, someone had pulled you from the water.
总之 有人将你从水中拉上来
"A son cruelly banished Despair of the daughter
“被残忍放逐之子 伤心且绝望之女”
Return, great avenger, With wings from the water."
“伟大复仇者的回归 从水中携带着羽翼”
There stands the despairing daughter.
那里站着伤心且绝望之女
You are the winged raven, returned from the sea,
你是长着羽翼的渡鸦从海中回归 而我…
but I'm the avenger of my family's ruin.
我 我是身负灭门血仇的复仇者
I pity you, Corvus.
我同情你 考乌斯
But you must die.
但你非死不可
Corvus Lestrange is already dead! I killed him!
考乌斯·莱斯特兰奇早就死了 是我杀了他
Accio!
速速飞来
My father owned a very strange family tree.
我父亲家有着非常奇妙的族谱
It only recorded the men.
上面只记录男性
The women in my family were recorded as flowers.
家族的女性以花朵代表
考乌斯·莱斯特兰奇
美丽
Beautiful.
孤立
Separate.
My father sent me to America with Corvus.
我父亲把我和考乌斯一起送往美国
Irma was to pose as a grandmother with two grandchildren.
伊尔玛假扮带着孙子们旅行的奶奶
Corvus never stopped crying.
考乌斯总是哭个不停
Do you have any news?
有任何消息吗?
All hands to station!
所有人员回工作岗位
Run to station!
立刻返回岗位
I never wanted to hurt him.
我从没想过伤害他
I only wanted to be free of him.
我只是想要摆脱他
Just for a moment.
哪怕只是一下
Just a single moment.
一下下就好
Give him to me.
把他给我
Everyone, to the lifeboats!
各位 前往救生船
They want us to put on life jackets.
他们叫大家穿救生衣
You didn't mean to do it, Leta.
你不是故意的 莉塔
So it wasn't your fault.
所以不是你的错
Oh, Newt.
不 纽特
You never met a monster you couldn't love.
你总能在怪物身上发现可爱之处
Leta...
莉塔
Do you know who Credence really is?
你知道克雷登斯的真实身分吗
Did you know when you swapped them?
在你调包的时候
No.
不知道
Queenie?
奎妮
They're pure-bloods.
他们是纯血巫师
They kill the likes of us for sport.
专门以杀我们这种人为乐
奎妮
Queenie?
Jacob!
雅各布
Honey, you're here! Hi!
甜心 你来了 嗨
Hi, hon. Hi.
嗨 甜心
Oh, honey, I'm so sorry.
甜心 我真抱歉
I never should have done it. I love you so much.
我不该一走了之 我好爱你
And you know that I love you, right?
你也知道我爱你 对吧?
- Yeah. - Good. Let's get the hell outta here.
对
很好 那我们闪人吧
- Yeah. - Good. Let's get the hell outta here.
Oh, no, wait a second.
不 等等 等一下
I just thought maybe we could hear him first.
我想先听听他要说什么
Just listen. That's all.
听听就好 如此而已
What are you talking about?
你在讲什么?
It's a trap.
这是陷阱
Yeah.
对
Queenie, the family tree. It's all been bait.
奎妮 族谱 只为了引我们入陷阱
We have to find a way out of here right now.
我们得快想办法立刻离开
You go find the others.
你去找其他人
你呢?
What are you gonna do?
I'll think of something.
我会见招拆招的
My brothers, my sisters,
兄弟们 姐妹们
my friends,
朋友们
the great gift of your applause is not for me. No.
你们热烈的掌声不该献给我
It is for yourselves.
而该献给自己
You came today because of a craving
你们来此是因为心里向往
and a knowledge
并深切了解
that the old ways serve us no longer.
墨守陈规对我们已不再管用
You came today because you crave something new.
你们来此是因为渴望新的东西
Something different.
不同的局面
It is said
很多人说
that I hate les non-Magiques.
我痛恨不懂魔法之人
The Muggles.
麻瓜们
- Vermin! - The No-Maj.
-害虫 -麻鸡
The Can't-Spells.
不施咒语者
我不恨他们
I do not hate them.
I do not.
完全不恨
For I do not fight out of hatred.
因为我不是为仇恨而战
I say the Muggles are not lesser,
我认为麻瓜并不是更低级
but other.
而是属性不同
Not worthless,
并非一文不值
but of other value.
而是价值不同
Not disposable, but of a different disposition.
不是不堪大用 而是别有用途
Magic blooms
魔法天赋
only in rare souls.
只在少数人身上绽放
It is granted to those who live for higher things.
只降临在对生命 有着更高追求者的身上
Oh, and what a world we would make for all of humanity.
若将世界交给我们统治 必能嘉惠全人类
We who live for freedom,
因我们全然为自由
for truth,
为真理
and for love.
为爱而生
It isn't illegal to listen to him.
听他演说又不犯法
Use minimum force on the crowd.
对群众要慎用武力
We mustn't be what he says we are.
我们不能成为他口中的那种人
The moment has come to share my vision of the future
大限已到 该向大家展示我所预见的未来了
若不揭竿起义
that awaits if we do not rise up
and take our rightful place in the world.
若不顺应天命将是何等境地
Not another war.
不要再打仗了
That is what we are fighting.
这就是我们要对抗的
That is the enemy.
这就是敌人
Their arrogance.
他们的狂妄自大
Their power lust.
他们的渴求权力
Their barbarity.
他们的粗鄙残暴
在他们将枪杆转向我们前 还有多少时间?
How long will it take before they turn their weapons on us?
Do nothing when I speak of this.
大家听我说就好 不要轻举妄动
You must remain calm
你们务必保持冷静
and contain your emotions.
控制自己情绪
There are Aurors here among us.
我们之中混杂了傲罗
Come closer, brother wizards. Join us.
靠近点 巫师兄弟们 加入我们
Do nothing.
按兵不动
And no force.
不要动武
They have killed many of my followers.
他们杀死我许多追随者
It is true.
那是事实
They confined me and tortured me in New York.
他们在纽约拘禁我 折磨我
他们滥杀女巫及巫师同胞
They had struck down their fellow witches and wizards.
For the simple crime of seeking the truth.
只因他们犯下追求真理的罪
For wanting freedom.
只因渴求自由
Your anger, your desire for revenge is natural.
你们的愤怒和复仇的渴望 是正常的
No!
不
Take this young warrior back to her family.
将这名年轻勇士的遗体 交还给她家人
Disapparate.
幻影移形吧
Leave.
都走吧
Go forth from this place and spread the word.
离开后记得传话出去
It is not we who are violent.
滥用暴力的人不是我们
Let's take him.
我们拿下他
Aurors, join me in this circle.
傲罗们 走进来加入我的行列
Pledge to me
宣告你的忠诚
your eternal allegiance,
顺我者昌
or die.
逆我者亡
Only here shall you know freedom.
唯有在这里才能享有自由
Only here shall you know yourself.
唯有在这里才能了解真我
Move! Run! Run!
闪开！ 快跑！
Play by the rules! No cheating, children.
要遵守游戏规则 不准作弊 孩子们
He knows who I am.
他知道我是谁
He knows what you were born, not who you are!
他知晓你的身世 但不了解你的为人
Credence!
克雷登斯
Queenie, honey. Queenie. You gotta wake up.
奎妮 甜心 你清醒点
Jacob.
雅各布
He's the answer.
他就是答案
He wants what we want.
我们与他目标一致
- No. - Yeah.
-不 -是的
This has all been for you, Credence.
这一切都是为了你 克雷登斯
Walk with me.
陪我一起去
Hon. No!
甜心 不
Walk with me!
陪我一起去
You're crazy.
你疯了
Queenie.
奎妮
No!
不
Queenie, don't do it!
奎妮 不要
Queenie.
奎妮
Queenie!
Mr. Scamander.
斯卡曼德先生
Do you think Dumbledore will mourn for you?
你觉得邓布利多会为你哀悼吗
Grindelwald! Stop!
格林德沃 住手
Leta...
莉塔
This one I believe I know.
我想我认识你
Leta Lestrange.
莉塔·莱斯特兰奇
Despised entirely amongst wizards,
被全体巫师界仇视
unloved, mistreated,
无人疼爱 饱受霸凌
yet brave, so very brave.
但仍勇敢 非常勇敢
Time to come home.
是时候该回家了
I love you.
我爱你
Go!
快走
I hate Paris.
我讨厌巴黎
Together, in a circle. Your wand into the earth.
大家一起围成圆形 魔杖遁地
Or all Paris will be destroyed.
否则巴黎将毁于一旦
Finite!
万咒皆终
I've chosen my side.
我早就选好一边站了
Come here. I've got you. I've got you.
过来 过来抱抱 过来抱抱
I think it's best if he speaks to him alone.
我想最好让他俩单独谈谈
奥地利 纽蒙迦德城堡
Is he frightened of me still?
他还是很怕我吗
You need to be careful.
讲话要小心
He's not sure he made the right choice.
他不确定自己的选择是否正确
Be very gentle with him.
要温柔地对待他
I have a gift for you, my boy.
我有礼物送给你 孩子
Is it true?
是真的吗
About Leta?
莉塔的事
Yes.
是
I'm so sorry.
太遗憾了
It's a blood pact, isn't it?
这是血盟 对吗?
You swore not to fight each other.
你俩立誓永不与对方为敌
How in the name of Merlin did you manage to get...
以梅林之名 你是怎么拿到…
Grindelwald doesn't seem to understand the nature of the things he considers simple.
格林德沃向来低估 他觉得不起眼的小东西
Can you destroy it?
有办法销毁吗
或许吧
Maybe.
或许
Would he like a cup of tea?
它会想要来杯茶吗
He'll have some milk.
它会想喝牛奶
Hide the teaspoons.
得把银汤匙藏好
You have suffered the most heinous of betrayals,
你多次遭遇最残忍的背叛
most purposely bestowed upon you by your own blood.
而且大多是由至亲手足
Your own flesh and blood.
跟你血脉相承的人刻意加注于你
And just as he has celebrated your torment,
如同他以你的痛苦为乐一般
your brother seeks to destroy you.
你的哥哥还想要赶尽杀绝
你家族传说，若是任何成员有难
There is a legend in your family that a phoenix will come to any member
who is in dire need.
就会有凤凰来搭救
这是你与生俱来的权利 孩子
It is your birthright, my boy.
我现在
As is
the name I now restore to you.
重新替你正名
Aurelius.
奥睿利乌斯
Aurelius Dumbledore.
奥睿利乌斯·邓不利多
We will go down in history together as we remake this world.
我们会因为重整世界 而一起名留青史
欢迎关注百度贴吧/微信公众号:神奇动物在哪里,神奇动物在哪里百度贴吧长期招募小吧,有意者加微信:18198102499(哈迷优先)
相约2021年 北京《哈利波特》主题公园 QQ观摩团正式开启:北京 158631939  上海 643698832  广州 483155735  深圳 540697531